Contact

București, Sector 1 +40746962776 (Mobile) biasinovschi@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/bogdaniasinovschi-a1a62bb9 (LinkedIn) biasinov.com (Personal)

Top Skills

React.js

Bootstrap

WSO2

Languages

Romanian (Native or Bilingual) English (Professional Working)

Certifications

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

Programming Analyst

Responsive Web Design

Project Management Fundamentals. Tools & Techniques

Bogdan Iasinovschi

Senior Integration Developer at Fortech Cluj-Napoca

Summary

I now act full time as a Senior Integration Consultant for the largest Pharmaceutical company in Europe, on behalf of an outsourcing company from Cluj-Napoca, with whom I collaborate.

Constantly tackling complex problems, finding appropriate solutions, and architecting various projects and tasks.

Working with all known data types and protocols, APIs, Jenkins, groovy scripts, developing Java custom tools, doing advanced macros in Excel, and many more.

Managing projects and driving the communications, with developers and managers of any levels throughout the company, for implementing various tasks, some of them critical and extremely sensitive.

Specialized in APIs - I am the WSO2 expert of the team. I provide guidance and assistance to all my colleagues that struggle with their tasks in this area.

Experience

Fortech

3 years 8 months

Integration Consultant April 2019 - Present (1 year 6 months)

Cluj County, Romania

Solutions architect responsibilities.

Working in the pharmaceutical industry for a major client located in Northern Europe, on behalf of Fortech.

I do mostly EDI processes. Involved in designing, developing, testing and documenting software solutions for data transfers between entities, with focus on quality and timely delivery.

Tools and technologies used:

#Axway B2Bi

#WSO2 API Manager

#Jenkins

#FitNesse

#Groovy

#SQL

#Java

#MBC

Integration Consultant

May 2017 - April 2019 (2 years)

Cluj County, Romania

Collaborating with Fortech SRL as an Integration Consultant. Our client is one of the largest pharmaceutical company in the world, with annual revenues of billions of dollars. In close contact and interacting on a daily basis with partners from all over Europe.

Involved in developing applications that enables us and our partners to exchange and transform our documents using a large variety of communication protocols and message formats.

Participate throughout the complete software development life cycle, including the design and architectural decisions, and focus on software quality through peer reviews, refactoring, continuous integration and deployment.

Cobol Programmer

February 2017 - May 2017 (4 months)

Cluj County, Romania

Hired after following a 6 weeks pre-employment training organized by the company.

Casa Boema

Assistant Event Manager

September 2015 - September 2016 (1 year 1 month)

Cluj County, Romania

Assisted the EM for the events held at Casa Boema's ballroom. Helped implementing beforehand all the prerequisites for a new event, depending on its type, and later coordinated and supervised the staff involved.

Education

Babeş-Bolyai University
Bachelor's degree, Economic Informatics · (2017 - 2020)

Academy+Plus
Software Developer, Computer Programming · (2016 - 2017)

Colegiul Silvic Bucovina Economics, Economics · (2005 - 2009)